On special days like today, Jay and I get a little excited.
今日みたいな特別な日に、ジェイとちょっとテンション上がるわ
Yeah, I'm happy.
うん、嬉しい
Isn't the scenery so beautiful?
めっちゃ景色きれいじゃない?
It's really good.
めっちゃいい
It's heartwarming.
ほのぼのする
Let's make it here.
ここで作ろうよ
Yeah, it's really good.
うん、めっちゃいい
Isn't this cold?
これ冷たくないかな?
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
Looks a little cold.
ちょっと冷たそう
It's cold.
冷てー
It's so cold.
めちゃくちゃ冷たい
Can you smoke it?
吸えられる?
Yeah.
うん
cold?
冷たい?
cold.
冷たい
This one.
これです
Let's give it as a present.
ちゃんとプレゼントしよう
Try opening it.
開けてみて
I hope it surprises you.
びっくりしてくれるといいな
Like this?
こんな感じ?
amazing!
すごい!
Pretty serious, right?
結構マジでしょ?
There are some things you can eat properly.
ちゃんと食えのもあるな
There is.
あるよ
cute.
かわいい
It's so cute.
めっちゃかわいいじゃん
Isn't it cute?
かわいいでしょ?
this.
これ
cute.
かわいい
golden ball.
金の玉
It might be cute.
かわいいかも
Isn't it cute?
かわいいでしょ?
This is cute so let's go with this.
これかわいくてこれにしよう
Shall we do this?
これしようか
So let's open this.
じゃあこれ開けていこう
Yeah.
うん
So beautiful.
めっちゃきれい
A proper Christmas tree.
ちゃんとクリスマスツリー
It turned out really clean.
めちゃくちゃきれいになったね
Mizuki is prettier though.
水木さんの方きれいだけど
I'm embarrassed.
照れる
It's true.
本当だよ
I'm embarrassed.
照れる
cute.
かわいい
It's so cute.
すごいかわいいね
This is crazy.
やばこれ
It feels good.
いい感じだね
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Small face.
顔ちっちゃ
Your face is amazing.
顔すげえちっちゃ
And aren't these boots too big?
そしてさ、この長靴でかすぎない?
Sorry, I made a mistake on this one.
ごめんね、これミスっちゃった
Isn't it so beautiful?
め っちゃ きれいじゃない?
Feels good.
いい感じ
Actually, I got another gift for Mizuki-chan.
実はさ、もう一個さ、水木ちゃんにプレゼントあって
Wow, super Christmas.
やば、超クリスマス
Do you understand?
わかる?
I think this will definitely suit you.
これ絶対似合うと思う
Would you like to try it on?
つけてみる?
good?
いい?
yes.
はい
Just look over here.
ちょっと こっち向いてよ
Wow, what is this mesutonakaime?
うわー、なんだこのメストナカイメ
Wow, that's super cute.
わー、超かわいい
It looks great on you.
すげえ似合うね
Doesn't it match your hair color?
なんか髪の色とちょうどよくない?
Is it just right?
ちょうどいい?
Yeah.
うん
good.
よかった
So cute.
すげえかわいい
The Christmas tree is also super cute.
クリスマスツリーも超かわいい
No, seriously.
いや、まじで
It's a nice day today.
今日いい日だね
Hey hey, reindeer-san, reindeer-san.
ねえねえねえ、トナカイさん、トナカイさん
Woof woof.
ワンワン
Huh, reindeer is a woof?
え、トナカイさんってワンワンなの?
I don't understand the sound of reindeer.
トナカイの鳴き声わかんない
Does it scream?
鳴くの?
Is it wan wan?
ワンワンなのかな?
Hmph, something like that.
ふんふん、みたいな
Wear this.
これ被って
picture?
え?
what?
何?
this?
これ?
Yeah.
うん
Because I'm a reindeer.
私トナカイであるから
Understood.
わかった
Well then, let's both wear these and walk around.
じゃあ 2人でこれ被って歩こうか
OK, I understand.
OK、わかった
My face feels moist.
顔がしっとりしてる
Is it moist?
しっとりしてるの?
Ah, it's amazing.
あー、すごいついてる
It's very ingrained.
すごい染みついてる
No, no, no.
だめだめだめ
There has to be some stains all the time.
いつでもシミミとかないといけない
What about the Christmas tree?
クリスマスツリーは?
Messed up.
めちゃくちゃ
Isn't it so beautiful?
すっごい綺麗じゃないの?
a
あ
Kantakuri-chan is spending October.
い かんたくりちゃん10月過ごしてる
You can even use your fingers.
指でもいっちゃうんだ
It's embarrassing, like.
恥ずかしいじゃん、みたいな
I'm very bloodshot.
すごい充血してる
real?
ほんと?
Ah, that feeling underneath.
あー、その下気持ち
Yeah.
うん
Reflective butt.
反 射してるお尻
Isn't it hard to lick there?
そこ舐めづらくない?
I wish I could step back more.
もっと後ろ下がったらいいと
If you had a face, I'd like you to look at it and lick it.
顔があったらずっと見ながら舐めてほしい
A person licking a popsicle.
アイスキャンディ舐めてる人
If you look at me, I'll be embarrassed.
目線やったら恥ずかしくなっちゃう
Ah, yes.
あー、そう
That feels good.
それ気持ちいい
I'm bleeding again.
また充血してる
It's not all included.
全部入ってない
I'm exhausted.
ヘトヘトになっちゃう
Christmas present?
クリスマスプレゼント?
I want to see it.
見たいな
fun.
楽しみ
Who?
何人?
What is it?
なんだ ろう?
Erotic one.
エロいやつ
It's Santa.
サンタさんじゃん
Yes, Santa Claus.
そう、サンタコス
This is just a little bit, if you'd like, could you come and check it out?
これちょっとさ、もしよかったら来てみてくれん?
Okay.
いいよ
Take me out of the bath.
風呂から出して
thank you.
ありがとう
If you don't mind, I'd like to give you a present,
もしよかったらさ、プレゼント渡しといてなんだけど、
On the other hand, I would like you to show me the replacement tree as my present.
逆に俺のプレゼントに生木替え見せてほしい
Stand up, stand up.
立って立って
I feel so bad standing up.
立ったほうがすげえかわいそう
What's the hat?
帽子は何?
What about the hat?
帽子は?
There are also feet
足元もある
Yo.
よ
amazing.
すごい
Santa came for Christmas.
ク リスマスにサンタさん来た
Aw, that's cute.
わ、かわいい
Try standing up, try standing up.
立ってみて立ってみて
Slowly, slowly.
ゆっくりゆっくり
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃかわいい
Illumi-chan is so small, I thought she was wearing a miniskirt.
イルミちゃんちっちゃいからさ、すげえミニスカコスかと思った
It's okay, it's okay.
ら、 大丈夫大丈夫
This is cute as it is.
これはこれでかわいい
sorry.
ごめん
I'm already tired, I just finished one session,
さっきさ、もう疲れてさ、ちょっと1回終わったんだけど、
Very erotic.
めっちゃエロい
TRUE?
本当?
Yeah, it turned out like this.
うん、こんな感じになっちゃった
Oh, are you worried about something now?
あ、なんか今気にしてる?
I wonder what Santa looks like.
サンタどんな感じかなって
Soooo cute.
すっげえかわいい
Isn't Pero below so cute?
下、ペロすっごいかわいくない?
Mizuki-chan.
みずきちゃん
Like Peko-chan.
ぺこちゃんみたいな
do?
やる?
Habit?
くせ?
It's annoying.
くせやる
I'm a little too horny.
ちょっとムラムラしすぎてちょっと
Did Santa ever touch your penis like this?
サンタさんってなんか、こんなふうにおちんちん触ってたっけ?
Isn't there such a Santa?
そういうサンタもいるんじゃない?
That's erotic.
エロいね
I gave you this as a present.
これプレゼントあげたし
I don't want to share it.
分かしたくないしね
Red.
赤の
Black.
黒の
Red and black?
赤黒の?
Yeah.
うん
A little bad Santa.
ちょっと悪いサンタさん
I'm already stiff.
もうチクビ立ってる
It's such a waste to take it off.
なんか脱がすのすごいもったいない
My chikubi is also standing.
俺のチクビも立ってるよ
Let Santa Claus do it.
サンタコスにやってもらおう
Take it off.
脱がすの
I'm so conflicted.
すごい葛藤してるぞ
What should I do?
どうしたらいいんだろう?
Santa Claus makes me feel better.
サンタコスのほうが気持ちよくする
Will you do that?
そうするの?
Yeah.
うん
This is what I like about Santa Claus
これがサンタコス好きなものなんだ
hey.
ね
Can I leave it for a while?
ちょっと 置いていい?
Yeah.
うん
Are you going to hide?
隠れそう?
Yeah.
うん
If you calm down and think about it.
落ち着いて考えたら
Yeah.
うん
I just stood up so badly.
さっきめちゃくちゃ中立ちちゃったんだけど
Can I check?
確認していい?
It's supposed to feel good enough.
十分気持ちいいことになってるじゃん
It's a swimsuit Santa.
水着サンタさんじゃん
Yeah.
うん
I hope you do something good.
いいことしてほしいな
Ah, it feels good.
あー気持ちいい
Ah, that feels good.
あ、それ気持ちいい
Become myself.
俺自体になる
I really felt like I was going to be forced to go.
本当に行かされそうだった
Swimsuit-chan also likes cream.
水着ちゃんはクリームも好きだけど
The order is different.
順 番違う
Santa will let you in.
サンタさんが入れてくれるんだよな
What is Santa?
サンタさんが何?
Santa is neutral.
サンタさんは中立に
Put this in from the cylinder.
これがシリンダーから入れて
Let's include Santa.
サンタさん入れてじゃん
Isn't it a gift from Santa?
サンタさんのプレゼント入れてるんじゃない?
Santa is too erotic.
サンタさんエロすぎる
Santa has great balance.
サ ンタさんすごいバランスがいい
Santa has good balance.
サ ンタさんバランスがいい
Leave it neutral.
それ中立に置いて
Do you have it?
持ってる?
I have it.
持ってる
It's my second time though.
2回目だけど